Support for NPR music comes from Capital
Capital
One, proud supporters of NPR music and
One 是 NPR 音乐和 Tiny Desk Contest 的忠实支持者，也是 NPR 音乐的赞助方
the Tiny Desk Contest. What's in your
。 你的钱包里有什么
wallet? Learn more at capitalone.com.
？ 了解更多信息，请访问 capitalone.com。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
[singing]
[歌唱]
&gt;&gt; Mics are on. Mics are on.
麦克风已开启。 麦克风已开启。
Mics.
麦克风。   是的
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
。   是的
&gt;&gt; Yeah. it's a pretty day. Let's go
。 今天天气真好。 让我们到
[music] outside [singing] and enjoy it.
户外去唱歌、听音乐，好好享受吧。
Yeah, yeah, yeah, let's go. What if you
好，好，好，走吧。 如果你
got something else in mind then I'm a
另有打算，那我就是个
fool. Yeah, yeah, baby, you [singing]
傻瓜了。 是啊，是啊，宝贝，你
know
知道
I'll take a chance.
我会冒险一试。
I'll take a
我愿意冒险尝试一下
&gt;&gt; [music]
音乐，
&gt;&gt; chance I'll take your hand
我会牵着你的手
and go there.
去那里。
Love isn't something that you earned
爱不是靠努力赢得的，而是你应得的
this deserve it. [music] Do you deserve
。  [音乐] 你配得上吗
it? Love is something I can give cuz I'm
？ 爱是我可以给予的，因为我
worth baby, [singing] baby all you worth
值得拥有，宝贝，[唱]宝贝，你值得拥有
amazing.
美好的一切。   我
I'm so taken in.
完全被你迷住了。
You're so lovely.
你太可爱了。
And I can't
我
see you.
看不见你。
Tell me what you want [singing]
告诉我你想要什么（唱歌）
now
现在
&gt;&gt; [music]
（音乐）
&gt;&gt; I know who you are.
我知道你是谁。
You're my superstar.
你是我的超级巨星。
&gt;&gt; [singing]
[唱歌]
&gt;&gt; I can't see
我看不见
you baby. Tell me what you [music] want
你，宝贝。 告诉我你想要什么样的音乐，
now I know
我现在知道
who you are. You're my superstar.
你是谁了。 你是我的超级巨星。
You know I liked him so much [music] it
你知道我有多喜欢他（音乐），它
turned into love and then the love back
变成了爱，然后爱又回来了，
the like now I feel like I burst in my
就像现在我感觉我冲进我的
nursery [singing] and named it so full
育婴室（唱歌），并给它取了个名字，充满了
of potential. He stands tall I feel his
潜力。 他身姿挺拔，我能感受到他
internal fire like the earth, moon, and
内心燃烧的火焰，如同天地万物
sea and the sky. Together we make
。 我们一起创造
[music] stars we are truly fly. I want
音乐明星，我们真的很棒。 我
to paint it. Take a picture of his soul.
想把它画下来。 拍下他灵魂的照片。
This story should be told.
这个故事应该被讲述出来。   你
See he's like everything I dreamed of
看，他简直就是我梦寐以求的样子，甚至
but better than the preview. Now
比预告片里还要好。 现在
everything you working on you got me
你做的所有事情都让我
saying this too like he food and I need
这么说，就像他是食物，而我需要
[singing and music]
[歌唱和音乐]
blood cuz he bleed. He real cuz I see
血液，因为他流血了。 他是真的，因为我亲眼看到了
it. It's all meant to be.
。 一切都是命中注定。
Remember how to make believe. Yo, the
记住如何假装。 哟，
brothers aren't your enemy you're in a
兄弟俩不是你的敌人，你只是
state of disbelief. Without your heart
难以置信而已。 没有你的心，
you'll never be.
你将不复存在。
So sister sing along with me cuz your
所以姐姐，跟我一起唱吧，因为你的
love is true.
爱是真挚的。
Your love
你的爱
is true. My love is honest and true
是真挚的。 我的爱真挚而纯粹，
and I can prove it baby. Prove it baby.
我可以证明给你们，宝贝。 证明给我看，宝贝。
My love is everything to you
我的爱就是我的一切，
and you're truly
你真的
amazing.
很棒。
I'm so taken with you.
我太喜欢你了。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; You're so good.
你真棒。
&gt;&gt; [singing]
[唱歌]
[music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; I can see you, babe.
宝贝，我能看到你。
&gt;&gt; [music and singing]
[音乐和歌声]
&gt;&gt; You're my superstar.
你是我的超级巨星。
superstar
超级巨星
&gt;&gt; [cheering]
[欢呼声]
[applause]
[掌声]
[music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; Oh, inside. Yo, yo.
哦，内心深处。 哟，哟。
&gt;&gt; [music and singing]
[音乐和歌唱]
&gt;&gt; Yo, all
哟，
you got to
你只需要
&gt;&gt; [singing]
[歌唱] 做
&gt;&gt; do is just [music] walk away.
[音乐] 走开。
You pass me by.
你从我身边经过。
&gt;&gt; [singing]
[唱歌]
&gt;&gt; Don't acknowledge
不要理会
my smile. Yeah.
我的笑容。 是的。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; When I tried to say hello.
当我试图说你好时。
&gt;&gt; [singing]
[唱歌]
&gt;&gt; Hello.
你好。
to you
给你，
Yeah, yeah, [music] yeah.
耶，耶，[音乐]耶。   是的
Yeah.
。
&gt;&gt; [singing]
[唱歌]
&gt;&gt; Just make my dreams come true.
就让我的梦想成真吧。
with you tonight.
今晚和你在一起。
tonight yeah, yeah
今晚，好啊，好啊，
Go.
走吧。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; Let me go.
放我走。
Take it. Take it.
拿着吧。 拿着吧。
&gt;&gt; [singing]
[歌声]
[music]
[音乐]
[crying]
[哭泣]
[cheering]
[欢呼]
[applause]
[掌声]
&gt;&gt; All right.
好。
&gt;&gt; [cheering]
[欢呼声]
&gt;&gt; All right, what we got?
好，我们得到了什么？
Oh.
哦。
Okay, it's the right time. It's the
好了，时机成熟了。 现在正是
right time. Right time for towels. Time
时候。 现在正是用毛巾的好时机。 该
for towels.
用毛巾了。
Is everyone feeling moist?
大家都感觉湿润吗？
&gt;&gt; [laughter]
[笑声]
I swear.
我发誓，现在放这首歌太早了。
It really is. Or maybe not.
确实如此。 或许并非如此。
Or maybe not.
或许并非如此。
&gt;&gt; [sighs]
[叹气]
&gt;&gt; Just [music] tell him.
就[音乐]告诉他吧。
Uh.
呃。   你
See I've been watching you for a while.
看，我观察你很久了。
Your smile and style. [music]
你的笑容和风格。  [音乐]
&gt;&gt; [singing]
[歌唱] 我
&gt;&gt; Want to know if I can
想知道我今晚是否可以
simply be with you for the night. All
和你在一起。
right.
好的。
Yo, is that [singing] all right?
哟，你唱歌还行吗？
Baby.
婴儿。
See there
看，
for [singing] me.
对我来说，唱歌只有一种音乐。   是的
Yeah.
。
And you
你
&gt;&gt; [singing]
（歌唱）
&gt;&gt; have made that abundantly
造就了那个丰盛的
&gt;&gt; babe.
宝贝。
Now we could
现在我们可以
take that step to see
迈出那一步，看看
said baby
这个宝宝
&gt;&gt; [singing]
[唱歌]
&gt;&gt; this is really
这真的会
gonna be
是
Now all you've got to do [music] is say
现在你只需要[音乐]说“
yes.
是”。
All you've got to do
你只需要对
&gt;&gt; [singing and music]
（唱歌和音乐）说“
&gt;&gt; yes.
是”就行了。
Said don't deny what you feel. Let me
有人说不要否认自己的感受。 宝贝，让我帮
undress you, baby.
你脱衣服。
&gt;&gt; [singing and music]
[歌唱和音乐]
&gt;&gt; Open up your mind and just
敞开你的心扉，
see I'm about to [music] let you know
看看我即将[音乐] 让你知道
you
你
make [singing] me so.
让我[歌唱] 如此。
Said all you got to do
他们说你只需要对
is [music]
音乐
say yes.
说“是”。
&gt;&gt; [singing]
[唱歌]
&gt;&gt; Don't deny what you feel. Let [music] me
不要否认你的感受。 宝贝，让我用音乐为
you, baby.
你宽衣解带。
&gt;&gt; [singing]
[唱歌]
&gt;&gt; Open up your mind and just
敞开你的心扉，
see I'm about to let [singing and music]
看看我即将让[唱歌和音乐]
you know
你知道
you make
你让
me so
我如此如此
so.
。
&gt;&gt; You make [music] me
你让我
&gt;&gt; so
如此
&gt;&gt; [singing]
歌唱。
&gt;&gt; so.
你让我变得
&gt;&gt; so
如此
so. [music]
平庸。  [音乐]
&gt;&gt; You make me
你让我
&gt;&gt; [singing]
[唱歌]
&gt;&gt; make me so
让我如此如此
so. [music]
。  [音乐]
So
还行吧
so.
。
So, so, so.
一般般，一般般。
Since love love [music and singing] you
因为你热爱音乐和歌唱，所以你
taking time.
抽出时间。
Better [music] take your
好的音乐，慢慢来，别着急
&gt;&gt; [singing]
唱歌
&gt;&gt; time.
。   是的
Yeah.
。
But I always do.
但我总是这样做。
You [crying] can't be
你（哭泣）不可能是
my babe.
我的宝贝。
Since I am
因为我正在
&gt;&gt; [singing]
[唱歌]
&gt;&gt; breaking up.
分手。
Listen,
听着，
but tonight
但今晚
since I am
因为我
&gt;&gt; [crying]
哭了，我是
&gt;&gt; meaning me.
说我自己。
Since it's going to be
因为
tonight.
今晚轮到我了。
Tonight, tonight.
今晚，今晚。
And all you got to
你只需
do is say
要说，
say [music and singing] yeah.
要说[音乐和歌唱]是的。
Don't deny what you feel. I'll let me
不要否认自己的感受。 宝贝，我会让
undress you, baby. [singing] Open up
你脱掉衣服。  [唱歌]敞开
your mind and
心扉，
express.
表达自我。
She I'm about to let you know
她，我正要告诉你，
you make me
你让我发出“
say oh.
哦”的感叹。
Oh.
哦。
Say don't deny what you feel. I'll
不要否认自己的感受。 我会
&gt;&gt; [singing]
（唱）
&gt;&gt; let me
让我
undress you, baby. Open up your mind and
脱掉你的衣服，宝贝。 敞开心扉，尽情
express.
表达。
She I'm about to let you know you make
她，我正要告诉你，你让
me
我
say make me.
说“让我”。
You you you make me.
你，你，你让我。
You you you
你你你
you make me.
你让我。
You make me
你让我
say you make me.
说出你让我说的话。
Babe, I'm
宝贝，我的
saying you make me.
意思是，是你让我这么做的。
No, you make me.
不，是你逼我的。
You make me.
你让我……
Make me.
让我。
You make [singing] me
你让我如此[唱歌]
so.
。
So.
所以。
So, so, so.
一般般，一般般。
&gt;&gt; Can I have you?
我可以拥有你吗？
Cuz I want to [singing] be with you
因为我今晚想和你在一起
tonight.
。
Hold tight and let me do you.
抓紧了，让我来好好伺候你。   就像
your dreams do.
你的梦境一样。
&gt;&gt; Oh.
哦。
&gt;&gt; Baby, can I have you?
宝贝，我可以拥有你吗？
&gt;&gt; just going to have you, baby?
就想拥有你吗，宝贝？
&gt;&gt; Can I just going to have you, baby? Can
宝贝，我能拥有你吗？
I
我
tonight.
今晚只想和 Cuz 一起唱歌。
Hold tight and let me do you.
抓紧了，让我来好好伺候你。   就像
your dreams do.
你的梦境一样。
&gt;&gt; Let me do you like your dreams do.
让我像你梦中那样对待你。
Can I just going to have you, baby?
宝贝，我能拥有你吗？
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; Can I have you?
我可以拥有你吗？
Just say [singing] yes.
就说（唱）“是”。
Say yes. Just say yes.
答应下来。 就说“好”吧。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; Hold tight. Hold tight. Let me do you.
抓紧了。 抓紧了。 让我来为你服务。
[singing] Yes.
[唱歌] 是的。
Say yes.
答应下来。
Just say yes.
就说“好”吧。
&gt;&gt; [singing]
[唱歌]
&gt;&gt; Yes.
是的。
Say yes.
答应下来。
Just say yes.
就说“好”吧。
&gt;&gt; [singing]
[唱歌]
&gt;&gt; Just say
就说“我愿意”
Yes.
。   是的
Say yes.
答应下来。
&gt;&gt; [singing]
[唱歌]
&gt;&gt; Yes. Say yes.
是的。 答应下来。
Say yes.
答应下来。
YES.
。
&gt;&gt; [cheering]
[欢呼声]
&gt;&gt; SAY YES.
答应我。
&gt;&gt; [applause]
[掌声] 是的
&gt;&gt; YES.
。   是的
BABY.
婴儿。
&gt;&gt; [applause]
[掌声]
[cheering]
[欢呼声]
&gt;&gt; OH.
哦。
BABY.
婴儿。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; OH.
哦。
BABY.
婴儿。
&gt;&gt; We need to uh
我们需要
talk about this thing, you know.
谈谈这件事，你知道的。
&gt;&gt; Baby.
婴儿。
&gt;&gt; How far we going to let this thing go.
我们究竟要让这件事发展到什么程度？
[singing] Babe,
[唱歌]宝贝，
we've been here before, baby.
我们以前来过这里，宝贝。
Babe,
宝贝，
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]天色已
&gt;&gt; it's getting late.
晚。
&gt;&gt; It's getting late.
天色已晚。
&gt;&gt; [screaming]
[尖叫]
&gt;&gt; Why'd you got to be
你为什么非得这样？
You're [music] uh
你（音乐）嗯，
&gt;&gt; You're beside me, you're [singing] just
你就在我身边，你（唱歌）只是，
&gt;&gt; You're just
你只是
&gt;&gt; watching me.
看着我。
And you're
你
wanting
想
eating me.
吃掉我。   是的
&gt;&gt; Yeah. [music]
。  [音乐]
&gt;&gt; But I'm afraid and you say
但我很害怕，你说
&gt;&gt; Don't be.
不要害怕。
Don't be.
别这样。
&gt;&gt; [singing]
[唱歌]
&gt;&gt; But now I'm afraid and you
但我现在很害怕，你
&gt;&gt; say
说
&gt;&gt; Don't be.
不要害怕。
Don't be.
别这样。
baby.
宝贝，我好害怕你会再次伤害我。
I'm afraid.
我耽心。
&gt;&gt; See, I've been [singing and music]
你看，我一直在（唱歌和听音乐）
thinking about you.
想着你。   我一直记着这件事
It's in my mind.
。
Far too [music] often for you to be here
你
at this time.
这个时候出现在这里实在太不合适了。
&gt;&gt; Babe.
宝贝。
&gt;&gt; One hand's [music]
一只手放在
on nine and the other's on my thigh.
九号位上，另一只手放在我的大腿上。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; Why?
为什么？
We've already played with the idea of
我们之前已经考虑过
you being here in the morning.
你早上来这里的情况了。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; Positioned for the crack of dawn.
已做好迎接黎明的准备。
before the yawning, but
打哈欠前的对话（音乐），但
&gt;&gt; [singing]
（唱歌）时间已经不
&gt;&gt; it's getting late.
早了。
I'm afraid.
我耽心。   天色已
&gt;&gt; It's getting late.
晚。
Why'd you got to be
你为什么非要
&gt;&gt; [singing]
唱这首歌？
&gt;&gt; You're beside me, you're
你就在我身边，
You're just watching me.
你就只是看着我。
And you're
你
wanting [music]
想让[音乐]
eating me.
吞噬我。
But I'm afraid and [music] you say
但我害怕，而[音乐]你说
&gt;&gt; Don't be.
不要这样。
Okay.
好的。
But I'm afraid and
但我害怕，
&gt;&gt; [singing]
你唱着歌说
Don't be.
不要害怕。
I'm so scared that you'll hurt me.
我好害怕你会伤害我。
How's about I
不如我
take [music] you to this space
带你回到
you left behind the day that you stopped
你不再
[music] smiling?
微笑的那天，回到你曾经离开的那个地方？
The day that the tears started falling.
泪水开始流淌的那一天。
[music]
[音乐]
But now we're talking and touching and
但现在我们谈笑风生，互相抚摸，
&gt;&gt; [singing]
[唱歌]
&gt;&gt; almost making sensual
几乎变得感性
You can uh
你能
taste [music]
尝到 [音乐]
the [singing] familiar
这 [唱歌] 熟悉的味道
The family are supportive of this moment
家人支持这一刻
but what's
但
by your movements [singing and music]
你的举动意味着什么 [唱歌和音乐]
cuz
因为天色已
It's getting late and
晚，
I'm afraid
我害怕
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐] 天色已
&gt;&gt; It's getting [singing] late.
晚 [唱歌]。
Why you got to be
为什么你要在
&gt;&gt; beside me
我身边唱歌，
and just watching and
只是看着我，
needing your wanting
渴望着你？
But I'm afraid and you say [music]
但我很害怕，你说（音乐）
Don't be.
不要害怕。
But I'm afraid and you say
但我害怕，你说
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
&gt;&gt; I'm afraid that you're going to hurt
我害怕你会伤害我。慢慢来
Take your time, babe.
，宝贝。   慢慢来，别着急
Take [singing] your time.
。
Take your time.
慢慢来。   请
Take [music] your time, please.
慢慢欣赏音乐。
&gt;&gt; [singing]
[唱歌] 慢慢来，别着急
&gt;&gt; Take your time before you take it.
。
Take your time, but please
慢慢来，但请务必这样
take it.
做。
Babe.
宝贝。
&gt;&gt; [singing and music]
[歌声和音乐]
I see those memories replayed.
那些记忆不断重现。
[music and singing]
[音乐和歌唱] 同一个
The same space. Same face.
空间。 还是那张脸。
Those same bodies, [singing] baby.
那些同样的身体，[唱歌]宝贝。
I know there's a better [music]
我知道
ending to your ending.
你的结尾可以配上更好的音乐。
&gt;&gt; [singing]
[唱歌]
&gt;&gt; Please, just take your time. Take your
请慢慢来。 慢慢来
time.
。
Take your time.
慢慢来。
&gt;&gt; [singing]
[唱歌]
I see those memories replayed.
那些记忆不断重现。
The same spaces. The same faces.
相同的空间。 同样的面孔。
Those same bodies, [singing]
那些同样的身体，[唱歌]
baby.
宝贝。
I know there's a better [music]
我知道
ending to your
你的
ending. [singing]
结尾可以配上更好的音乐。  [唱歌]
Please, just take your time. [music]
请慢慢来。  [音乐]
Take your time.
慢慢来。
before you take it.
拿之前别着急。
Take your time, but please take it.
慢慢来，但请务必这样做。
Take take [music] take take
拿拿[音乐]拿拿拿
Take your time before
慢慢来，在你……之前……（
&gt;&gt; [screaming]
尖叫）……开始……开始……开始……开始……开始……
Take take [singing] take
（唱歌）……开始……在
Take your time before you
你……之前……开始……开始……开始……开始……开始……开始……开始……
Don't please me.
不要取悦我。
It's getting late.
天色已晚。
Take your time before
请慢慢来，然后
&gt;&gt; [screaming]
[尖叫]
[music]
[音乐]
[cheering]
[欢呼]
[applause]
[掌声]
&gt;&gt; Okay.
好。
Is everybody okay?
大家都还好吗？
Keep Keep your space now. Keep your
现在就保留你的空间。 保持
space.
距离。
&gt;&gt; Okay. [laughter]
好的。  [笑声]
&gt;&gt; Just get it. All right.
买吧。 好的。   是的
Yeah. Lift it.
。 把它举起来。   是的
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Uh. Uh. Yeah. Come on.
。 是的。 是的。 呃。 呃。 是的。 快点。
Woah.
哇哦。
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐]
[singing]
[唱歌]
&gt;&gt; I say what's up.
我说，你好吗？
&gt;&gt; Yo, what's up?
哟，最近怎么样？
&gt;&gt; What's up with you?
你怎么了？
&gt;&gt; You feeling good?
你感觉还好吗？
&gt;&gt; We feeling too.
我们也感同身受。
&gt;&gt; We going to mess right now with this
我们现在要对这个
groove.
节奏进行一些调整。
&gt;&gt; I step on one.
我踩到了一个。
&gt;&gt; You step on two.
你踩到了两块。   是的
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
。   是的
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐] 是的
&gt;&gt; Yeah. [singing]
。  [唱歌] 是的
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
。   是的
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐] 是的
&gt;&gt; Yeah. [music]
。  [音乐] 是的
&gt;&gt; [music]
[音乐] 是的
&gt;&gt; Yeah. [music]
。  [音乐] 是的
&gt;&gt; Yeah.
。 好的。 没错，就是女歌手
all right.
。
From London's SE5 Philly West Side just
来自伦敦 SE5 费城西区，只
TO BRING THE FIRE.
为带来激情。
FROM LONDON'S SE5 [music] PHILLY WEST
来自伦敦 SE5 区 [音乐] 费城
Side just to bring the fire.
西区，只为带来激情。
All right. We are Floe wit tree and we
好的。 我们是 Floe wit tree，我们都
all right. Floe wit sistah, all right.
很好。 和妹妹一起漂浮，好的。
Songstress, all right. Just letting them
没错，就是女歌手。 只是想让他们
know it's [music] all right.
知道音乐没问题。
Floe wit tree and we all right. Floe wit
浮木和树，我们都很好。 和
sistah,
妹妹一起漂浮，
all right. Songstress, all right.
好的。 没错，就是女歌手。
Letting y'all know, know, know, know,
让你们都知道，都知道，都知道，都
know.
知道。
&gt;&gt; [cheering]
[欢呼声]
[applause]
[掌声]
&gt;&gt; Give it up FOR THE BAND.
为乐队欢呼！
[cheering]
[欢呼声]
&gt;&gt; SHOUT OUT TO LIVERPOOL, SOUTH LONDON,
向利物浦、伦敦南部、
JAMAICA, all of our family and friends.
牙买加以及我们所有的家人和朋友致敬。
We love you.
我们爱你。
&gt;&gt; [cheering]
[欢呼声]
[applause]
[掌声]
&gt;&gt; Thanks for watching. Support for NPR
谢谢收看。  NPR
Music comes from Rivian, makers of
Music 得到了 Rivian 的支持，Rivian 是一家生产
all-electric adventure vehicles designed
全电动探险车的公司，其设计充分考虑了
with the planet and future generations
地球和子孙后代的福祉
in mind.
。